Always Follow Your Dream
Will is a drama, family film directed by Ellen Perry.
Brennan is Liverpool's number one fan, able to recite facts ad infinitum about the club and at a public school in the south of
England since his father Gareth is emotionally unable to care for him following the death of Will's mother.
Gareth appears one day out of the blue with tickets for Liverpool's
trip to the 2005 Champions League Final in Istanbul.
Gareth, played by Damian Lewis.
Davey, played by Bob Hoskins.
Nancy, played by Rebekah Staton.
Will, played by Perry Eggleton.
Simon, played by Kieran Wallbanks.
Finch, played by Malcolm Storry.
The following is an overview of the events of 2011 in film, including the highest-grossing films,
film festivals, award ceremonies and a list of films released and notable deaths.
More film sequels were released in 2011 than any other
year before it, with 27 sequels released.
The film explores themes of sports, football
(soccer), woman director, liverpool fc.
The tone is emotional.